This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas
in search of the One Piece,
a legendary treasure left behind by Gold Watcher,
King of the Pirates.
Bucky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber
after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now, this is exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the government prison, Impel Down.
Now, with Team Bay and Crocodile at his side,
they're in the midst of a huge battle on level four.
This is the Great Fortress of Hell!
None shall pass!
Now be gone!
Refusal to be defeated!
Sirius Hannibal!
Who's this doofus?
Why'd he open the doors all the way?
That's Hannibal.
He's the vice-warden of the prison.
Fire!
Take a look!
We've got a thousand troops armed with a thousand cage-shot bazookas
packed into the stairway to level three.
It's the end of the line!
This is as far as you go!
What's with the vice-warden? He's all fired up!
You think that's another impostor?
How's it going?!
Huh?
In order to guarantee the safe future of all innocent citizens,
you, Straw Hat, must be eradicated!
I hereby sent you to death on behalf of the Warden!
That can't be the same Vice Warden I know.
Move!
Try and make me!
I'm in a hurry!
Yes!
Nice move!
Hey, and look at his halberd!
That's the Bloodsucker!
Bastard!
You shouldn't underestimate me!
He actually knows what he's doing!
I'm here! I thought he was only good at complaining!
Yeah!
YEEE!
Heya! Heya! Heya! Heya! Heya! Heya! Heya!
That's right! The Heya Hustle Dance! The Infernal Hell Wheel!
If I don't get the hell out of my way, I'll make you! I gotta save him!
You gotta be joking!
What kind of vice-woman would I be if I stepped aside just because an inmate asked me?
Second gear!
Huh?
Now come, come!
Jack!
We've been praying you'd arrive.
You've got to do something, Warden Magellan.
Where are the ringleaders behind this uprising?
They're in front of the staircase to level three,
but that's on the opposite side of the floor from here,
and we're going to have to fight our way through the riot.
So far, Vice Warden Hannibal has kept them back,
but who knows how long he can hold out.
No, Vice Warden!
He took me down so easily.
I don't even deserve to call myself Vice Warden.
If only Magellan were here.
Reporting for my first day as jailer, sir.
Sir, my, my, my name is Hannibal.
They weren't kidding when they said you look like a cobra.
What?
Jeez, are you trying to hurt my feelings?
I've got a feeling you're the only person that's going to be able to keep this snake in line.
Well, Magellan?
You can count on me, sir.
Geeze, that jerk Magellan.
He's got some nerve assigning a genius like me to level one.
Really?
Any idiot could handle the intake for new inmates.
The next one's arrived.
Oh, okay!
This one's got a 50 million berry bounty.
The pirate Miss Olive.
She's extremely dangerous.
Take extra precaution with her.
Just my time!
Why did I say that out loud?
Well, he was easy.
Like every other man.
Wait, I have to strip down naked?
Could you at least be polite enough to look away?
Uh, sure!
So, dressed yet?
Um, not yet.
Such a fool.
I couldn't agree more.
Stop!
Please!
No!
What the hell are you doing letting your guard down?
Ouch!
It doesn't matter if you're working on level one or six.
All duties are equally important here.
If one person fails, the entire system fails.
You must keep that in mind at all times.
Let go!
I'm not through with you yet!
Whoa!
You won't pass!
Yes!
Follow the vice warden's lead!
Don't hold back!
Move it!
I'm gonna save my brother!
Yeah!
You should worry about saving your own life!
To my way!
Bastard...
You are not getting past me!
Tom's of...
Jack's kill!
Don't move!
Just quit already!
Dammit! I don't have time for this crap!
You're not getting past me!
You're the king of diarrhea! You hear me?
You should wear a toilet seat for a crown!
He's been screaming insults for more than 30 minutes now!
That's our Captain Buggy! He's the best!
Your mom should have flushed you, you turd!
I'm all out of insults. It had a good run, but you can only stretch this turd thing so far!
You doing okay there?
Magellan's pretty tough to eat up all this abuse, huh? I gotta take a quick bathroom break.
Wait, you don't mean... did he go and give himself diarrhea?
Nope, gotta piss, that's all.
Good idea! We haven't peed in hours!
What the hell should I do?
If I can't get through that wall of poison, not only are we stuck here, but my reputation will be ruined too!
That ain't what's it gonna take!
What a joke! That's supposed to stop odds?
Try they might to avoid destiny, fate marches on nonetheless...
Liberation!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
That's a long link you're taking there!
Captain Buggy, you gotta see this!
Is something wrong?
The wall... it's vanished!
What did you say?
How did this... happen?
There's not even a single trace of the poison left!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Huh?
My barrage of devastating insults finally got to him!
That's right! It was a pain, but it paid off!
Amazing! So you really were battling Magellan's venom with your venomous tongue!
You're a badass!
Cool! The being was also part of your attack, right?
No. There's nothing about this that makes any sense.
All right! I've destroyed the blockade! Fallen behind and follow me to freedom!
I told you! I'm in a hurry! Get out of my way!
I tell I will!
Just move, you pot-bellied weirdo!
You're not taking a single step!
You don't have time for this! I got the important things to do!
All right! I'm leaving here! And I'm saving it!
You keep saying you want to save your brother like at some noble quest!
But I know you're nothing but scum! Both of you!
All the pirates and rebels here, you don't give a damn about anyone but yourselves!
Stop my sword and you've done enough!
Don't stand up!
You're gonna get killed!
As long as scum like you are free to terrorize the seas,
decent people can't even sleep at night because they're worried about losing their loved ones!
This jail was built to protect them!
Locking up evil criminals like you is the only way to give them some peace of mind!
This fortress is the floodgate of hell!
And I won't let the world drown in terror by letting prisoners break free!
So like I already said, you won't take a single step!
Bye, sport!
The only thing I want is to save my brother! So move it!
You're too dumb to understand!
Bye, sport! Help us!
Hey! What's happening in there?
Buttercork in it already!
All this blathering about what's right and wrong in the world!
If you'd look at the world from outside your damn prison,
it seems not so black and white!
So cut the crap!
Huh?
That guy! I met him in Jaya!
the player!
Huh?
Uh...
Oh, wow!
Wow!
Oh, wow. Wow.
Well, ain't this a fine trip down memory lane.
Looks like we got you boys right in the middle of something.
Hello, teach. Mind telling us what the hell you're doing here?
Huh? Well, or do you only answer to Blackbeard now?
Jinbei.
Hey, hey, what's with the hostility? Why don't you loosen up those fists there?
Oh, yeah, I forgot you and Ace are pretty tight.
But hey, there's not much point in caring about him anymore.
Blackbeard.
I can't right now. I'm chasing someone.
He's a pirate named Blackbeard.
The dreams of pirates will never end!
According to this, a pirate named Blackbeard defeated Ace and gave him up to the world government.
In return, they invited him to be a warlord.
Blackbeard, huh?
I see.
Huh?
So you're...
Blackbeard!
Huh? Oh, right. I guess I never gave you my name, did I?
Z-
Long time no see, straw hat, Luffy.
Hey, I know how you feel.
I was surprised myself when I heard you were my old commander's baby brother.
What are you doing down here? You're gonna miss the big show.
Don't you want to be there for your brother's public execution?
Z-
And this washed up former warlord over here.
Yeah, I mean you, crocodile.
I heard you got your ass handed to you, but I didn't know straw hat, Luffy, was the one to do it.
Funny thing is, I was trying to take crocodile's place as a warlord at the time.
So killing you was about the best way I could think of to show the government I was worthy of the position.
Let's stop beating around the bush now, shall we?
Even if you play dumb, I know you're a crafty bastard.
There's only one reason for me to be here, and you know what it is.
Whitebeard's days are numbered and you know it.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates.
First, I'm headed off to Water 7 to kill straw hat Luffy as a special gift to the world government.
Wouldn't hurt to have you along for the fun.
Luffy, huh?
You're out of your mind.
Oh, you know him?
Of course I know him, you sack of crap.
I'm not gonna let you kill my little brother.
And yet here you are.
Fate decided to save you instead.
Ace had been chasing after me to get revenge for my so-called crime on Whitebeard's ship.
And I had been chasing you.
Of course I couldn't team up with him to kill you, but it all worked out.
Because we both got the fight we wanted.
If I surrender to you, then I can never call myself a man again.
I won't submit and I won't live with regrets no matter what.
You got that, stupid?
Z-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
The Sun Against Darkness, huh?
Only one can win!
I'll make Whitebeard the king.
Or die trying.
Z-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Aaaaaaah!
Henry ain't it. If he'd let us get away,
he'd not only disgrace Whitebeard's name,
but he'd also be turning his back on his brother and leaving you to die.
There is no such thing as coincidence when it comes to fate, truly.
Yeah, and you got lucky, kiddo. You weren't fated to die.
Our captain achieved his goal of becoming a warlord thanks to your brother,
so you're thoroughly useless to us now.
Whee-ha-ha! Ole's put up a brave fight,
but it just didn't work out for him.
Better make sure you pay your humble respects at his grave, Straw Hat.
He went and took your place for you,
because if it weren't for your brother,
you'd be dead and he'd be walking free.
If that's the truth, try to kill me now!
Huh?
Gom Gom!
Jack!
Aaaaaaah!
Amidst the chaotic jailbreak, Luffy finds himself face to face with Blackbeard.
The pie-loving pirate then reveals that he was the one who captured Ace and turned him into the Navy.
Ignoring more pressing concerns, Luffy loses control and is provoked into battle.
On the next One Piece, Jet Pistol of Anger, Luffy versus Blackbeard,
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Archede- bunny!
Archede- bunny Moons.
Archede- Ribe!
OSdli-